ALBERTO SOLDIVIERO

DETAILS

San Giovanni Valdarno (AR)



+39 392 074 3299



✓ albertosoldiviero@gmail.com



01/09/2001

LANGUAGES

Italian - First language English - B1

SKILLS

I am a web developer with skills in HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and TypeScript. I have been using Angular for two years in a professional setting to develop web applications. I also have a basic knowledge of React, acquired through a course, and a foundational understanding of Node.js for creating REST APIs.

EDUCATION

Graduating from art high school, high school "BenedettoVarchi"

Montevarchi

2015-2020

Audiovisual Multimedia address

course "Web developer", ASEV

Empoli

2020-2021

Bases of programming, Web design

Academy "Junior Front-End Developer" Software Inside

march 2022 - june 2022

Java-script, Type-script React, Angular

WORK EXPERIENCE

Be DigiTech Solutions

june 2022 - jan 2023

Six-month internship. I participated in the development of an Angular project for a web application aimed at providing insurance services.

Antica Bottega Digitale

Arezzo

jan 2023 - Current job

I am responsible for developing various types of web applications using Angular.